[KING OF COMEDY]
[Episode 6]
What are you looking at?
Don't look.
What's wrong?
No, no.
Ke, don't look.
What's wrong?
Don't block it.
I love Shapu!
Everyone, go to Shapu Village!
But you have to admit,
it's quite interesting.
Right?
I've had
quite a busy night.
Absolutely brilliant.
Where are you going?
Don't jump into the sea!
I have to shoot a few B-roll shots later.
I'll get back to work.
Go ahead.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
Thanks.
Okay, okay.
Liu, come here.
Okay.
What did I say?
See? I told you so.
Right?
When it comes to cultural tourism,
we can give it a try.
There's a lot of potential,
right? Keep working hard.
Keep it up.
That's not what you said before.
You said we were playing house.
Well...
Kids will grow up.
Right?
So you mean...
you're willing to give us
a little more time?
Thank you.
Did he have to go that far?
He didn't take it off later, did he?
No, he didn't.
He really goes all out.
-Yes.
-She must've given him a lot of money.
Otherwise, he wouldn't have done this.
He's not a problem,
but that old man is.
I mean the man who inspired Yin Tinchiu.
He's a big problem.
That old man is Chen Junnan's father.
Yes.
Isn't Chen Junnan one of our guys?
Chen Junnan is very sly.
I suspect he's playing both sides now.
This can't go on.
Gao Jiaoqi,
I think you should go
to Shapu Village right now
and take over
Chen Junnan's work completely.
And
most importantly,
make sure this old man
doesn't shoot anything else for them.
Understood.
Mr. Huang.
I actually have a way
to make this old man disappear completely.
Zhen,
I really don't understand
Zhou Ke anymore.
What do you think he's doing this for?
He feels guilty
and wants to make up for it.
But he's going too far.
How guilty must he be?
If he'd known this would happen, he
shouldn't have done it in the first place.
Don't mention him again.
We're even now.
Right.
Our time together is over.
Where's Zhou Ke?
Have you seen Zhou Ke?
Mr. Maling, what's wrong?
This despicable outsider
is such a bastard.
Did he lie to you, too?
He deceived my heart.
He betrayed my trust.
He actually threw the precious
"I Hear You" I gave him
into a sugarcane field.
If I hadn't gone treasure hunting,
I would have been fooled by him forever.
Look.
The sound quality is all messed up.
No, Mr. Maling.
First of all,
you lent this to him.
I didn't handle it.
You can't ask me for compensation.
He's not here right now.
You said
you wanted to buy me out.
Don't you like Zhen?
Why are you trying to ruin things for her?
What are you playing at?
I'm definitely tearing down the house.
I'll give you another 2000.
Just be a good little spy.
Is that clear?
I, Zhou Ke,
refuse.
I won't join forces with villains.
I hate bad guys the most.
Zhen.
Did we misunderstand him?
No.
We wronged him.
[Shacheng Transport Station]
Why are you wearing my clothes?
Do I have a choice?
My clothes are all gone.
So I can only wear yours.
Is it necessary
to cover yourself up like this?
I'm afraid people will recognize me.
This covers me up well.
Otherwise, my leopard underwear
would be a dead giveaway.
-Alright. Alright.
-It's way too recognizable.
You should cover yourself, too.
Why should I cover myself?
Cover...
Cover yourself up a bit.
You... Don't... I...
You are even more recognizable.
Cover yourself up a bit.
You're talking nonsense.
Who could recognize me?
It's fine. Just cover up a bit,
Ximei!
How did you recognize me?
You are highly recognizable,
right,
Mr. Zhou?
Where is he?
Over there.
Mr. Zhou!
That was a little episode.
Right.
An episode.
Since Mr. Zhou comes back,
you must have
some new plans.
You saw right through me.
Then I will also make 3 points.
Okay.
Chen Xingwang.
Still Chen Xingwang.
Look.
With Chen Xingwang as our trump card
and our ticket to going viral,
we're guaranteed
to succeed.
-Chen Xingwang.
-Chen Xingwang
Chen Xingwang.
Chen Xing—
Where are we going?
I'll take you
to an MCN company.
("C" sounds like "stuff" in Chinese.)
If I'd known,
I wouldn't have eaten so much.
I can't stuff anything else in.
Not stuffing it.
Okay, don't eat then.
How is it?
How do you like the new toy?
Junnan.
Our village is about to be demolished.
Don't you think
it's a little inappropriate
to set up something this big?
What do you know?
The demolition is one thing.
I still gotta make money while I can.
Come on, hang this up.
Junnan, this is too expensive.
10 yuan for 30 minutes?
Who would pay for it?
It's cheap enough.
People would even play for 15.
You know nothing.
Hang it up. Hang it up.
Chen Junnan!
-Chen Junnan!
-Here they come again.
Chen Junnan!
Protect me!
Why are you here again?
Where did you take your dad?
What? Take him where?
You won't admit it?
You're pretending?
You're putting on an act!
I really don't know.
You can't stand to see us
do well, can you?
Tell us where you took him.
We just got Mr. Chen going viral,
and you sent him away?
Who sent him away?
Keep pretending.
Talk!
I'll prove it.
I really don't know.
Hey, Junnan.
If you sent him away, just tell them.
Cut it out.
I'll call my dad.
Call him.
I'll call him now.
Call him now.
Put it on speaker.
-Put it on speaker.
-Okay!
[Daddy]
Hello, Dad.
[Chen Xingwang]
[Chen Junnan]
Hello?
Dad, where did you go?
[Hangzhou Expressway Exit,
Yuhang District]
I'm on my way to Hangzhou.
Hangzhou?
An MCN
[Personal resume: Chen Xingwang]
[Hobbies: Performance]
signed me.
I think it's a nine-year deal.
[Party B: Chen Xingwang]
I... I don't know.
9 years?
Hello? Hello?
Why'd you sign such a long contract?
Wait, are you coming back?
I won't be back anytime soon.
When you make it big,
don't forget me.
Okay.
Drop the act.
Thank you.
Thank you all.
My dad wouldn't have
made it without you.
And without my dad,
there'd be no me.
Zhen.
Thank you.
Don't harass my sister.
Don't harass his sister.
Thank you.
Don't be a flirt.
Sorry.
Put it back.
How do you know it's not expired?
You're just eating it.
I haven't tried it before.
I want to taste it.
How many times have I told you two?
Can you mind your manners?
We are about to
take off.
Mr. Gao.
Mr. Gao,
why are you here?
How did it go?
It's done.
What do you mean it's done?
I spent money
to sow discord between them.
The four of them have fallen apart.
The four of them
are closer than ever now.
That's only temporary.
Right.
I sent my dad,
my own father,
away.
He will never come back.
I sent
your dad away.
Wait, you sent him away.
Why didn't you tell me?
He's my biological father.
Do you know
how much your dad can make out there?
No matter how much he makes,
he's still my dad.
Dad.
Sit, sit, sit.
I don't know what Mr. Huang sees in you.
You can't get anything right,
and I have to clean up your mess.
What are your orders, Mr. Gao?
What I promised you,
I will definitely deliver.
But
I have one condition.
From today on,
I'll be in charge of everything
in Shapu Village.
You all have to listen to me.
Understood.
If you hear anything,
report to me immediately
at my mobile office.
Car House,
House, house car,
House... Car...
Stuck.
Keep me posted.
Understood.
Take care, Mr. Gao.
Don't eat too much of this.
Here it is.
Here.
Have some fish balls
while they're still hot.
Thank you, thank you.
Ms. Lin, eat it while it's hot.
Have some
while you wait for Mr. Zhou.
-Okay.
-Eat.
Done changing?
How is it?
Do my clothes fit you?
They're...
They're okay. They're just... a little...
a little long.
The pants are a little loose.
Mr. Zhou.
From today on,
we're
like brothers.
Yes, yes.
I, Chen Jiahao, give you my word today.
You can wear anything
in the wardrobe at home.
My wardrobe.
Okay.
It's fine. I'll just
wear them for a while to get by.
My clothes are all...
Mr. Zhou,
there was no time to cook,
so I just heated up some fish balls.
Just make do with them.
Just consider this
a small welcome-back meal for you.
There is nothing small about this.
To be honest,
we've been craving this.
Yeah, we really like this.
As long as you like it.
Delicious.
That's the taste.
So good.
What a welcome.
As soon as we came back,
Mr. Chen passed away.
No,
he's just gone.
That's not right, either.
He just
vanished.
He quit.
Right, he quit.
It's all Chen Junnan's fault.
I think he's definitely behind this.
Actually,
I was just thinking about it.
Let
bygones be bygones.
We have to move forward.
Since
our village has
the real-life Yin Tinchiu,
maybe
the people who inspired
the other characters
might also be hiding
right here in our village.
Right.
Are there
any other people
who inspired the other characters?
We can just keep making videos with them.
To be honest,
since Mr. Chen's video
went viral online,
all our villagers,
well,
rushed to copy him.
-And it was
-It's a good thing.
a complete disaster.
Ms. Zicai in our village
posted a video
claiming to be the inspiration for Dujuan.
She suffered overwhelming
cyberbullying.
It seems
this path really won't work.
How about
we just
do the same thing
and make another one?
No.
Even if we could pull off
a fake like this,
it might not work,
and we could end up hurting the villagers.
Don't fake things
or take some shady shortcut.
I'm with Ms. Zhen on this.
To be honest,
I really did it for my house at first.
But now that the villagers
trust us so much,
we can't let them down.
Do you have any other ideas?
Then we might have to think this through.
But not for too long.
Mr. Zhou.
After all, Mr. Chen's popularity
will pass quickly.
We can't keep relying on you
dancing shirtless to get views,
can we?
Yes.
Zhou Ke.
Mr. Zhou.
This is...
Mr. Shark.
-Hello, Mr. Shark.
You... well...
well...
you have my style from back in the day.
Let me tell you.
Thank you.
You know what?
My daughter
has been living in the city for many years
and never came back.
Now,
she saw in the video
that our Shapu Village is popular,
and now she wants to come back
and open a guesthouse.
Jiajia is coming back?
Yes.
Here.
Take it.
No, I can't.
I can't take it.
Take it.
Keep it.
You keep it.
Let me tell you,
these are the clothes my daughter wore
when she was little.
They are very good.
Pick whatever you like.
Pick?
Pick some to wear?
No need, sir.
My daughter is coming back.
My daughter is coming back!
Take it easy, sir. Take care.
Careful, careful.
My daughter is coming back.
That's great.
He is so nice to you.
Go back and pick some to wear.
Right.
I learned 3 things
from what happened with Mr. Shark.
What are they?
First,
Mr. Zhou's influence
is very great.
Yes.
You're the pride of Shapu Village now.
This dance—
everyone in the village, young
and old, knows this dance.
Second,
you know what?
A reporter today
were going door to door
asking about Mr. Zhou.
Look at that.
Third,
everyone says you're not very tall,
but you've got incredible explosive power.
Wait.
You just said a reporter were looking
for me from door to door?
Yes.
Did they want to interview me?
Really?
I have an idea.
I know how to expand our influence.
Do you have that reporter's contact info?
Yes.
Call them.
Stop it!
That's some serious power from your core!
All right.
That's a good one.
L-Let's go over it one more time.
Okay.
Go back!
Good.
Very good.
You two.
Mr. Gao, what brings you here
so late?
I have something
to talk to you about.
We'll have to pass.
It's time for us to get off work.
No, I mean...
What time do you get off work?
Those guys are still working there.
Sorry.
We should get off work.
I'm sorry.
Let's talk about it tomorrow.
It's okay.
Please
come to my mobile office for a chat.
Office?
I won't go to that kind of place.
Your mobile office
is quite small.
Okay.
Chief, let's eat.
I'll pass.
We have discipline.
Just get straight to the point.
No.
Back then, when you went to such lengths
to get us to bring in investors,
you weren't saying that.
You can't say that.
It was Mr. Huang
who approached me first back then, right?
It doesn't matter who made the first move.
Didn't you give us your full support?
Yes.
Then you can't just turn around
and change your mind
now that Zhen and the others
have finally got things going.
Doesn't that make you a fence-sitter?
Don't say that.
I am the village chief.
So
I will support whoever
can bring more benefits
to the villagers,
right?
The villagers think
they're not getting enough money,
so they want us to pay more.
No, no, no.
That's not what I mean.
Then what do you mean?
Y-You two
are overthinking.
You see,
I am just a village chief,
right?
What am I?
If the villagers support you,
you're somebody.
If the villagers don't support you,
you're nobody.
No, don't say that to me.
Okay, in that case,
we'll just go door
to door and win them over.
I won't stop you.
You are free to do as you please.
If there's nothing else,
I'll go back first.
No need to see me out.
This is really nice.
A mobile office.
It's good.
I'll get one, too.
Done.
The reporter is all set.
Really?
That's great.
I think Ke is right.
Having
the reporter come
could actually be our way out.
Then we'll succeed.
Zhen,
about buying followers...
Stop.
Haven't you already apologized?
No need to apologize again.
I wanted to say,
I bought followers
because
when we first came here,
I thought you and your brother
didn't look very smart.
Deep down, I never thought
you could make this
work.
So,
I took it upon myself to buy followers.
Because of this,
Zhou Ke
was... was really mad at me.
I still want to sincerely say
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
To be honest, at first,
I didn't trust you, either.
But after going through so much,
I believe in you,
and I believe in myself.
I believe in you, too.
Y-You might look tiny...
Well.
Tiny...
Okay.
Anyway, now that we've found a way out,
things will definitely get better.
Just... really, really great!
Don't wake them up.
We won't.
Ke might look unreliable,
but he's actually got a lot on his mind.
Why is he so short?
It's all that stuff weighing him down.
He's probably too worried
to sleep right now.
Actually, Jiahao is the same.
He looks a bit clueless,
but he's actually super thoughtful.
He's never experienced
anything this complicated.
I guess right now,
he's hiding under the covers, crying.
Stop crying.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it.
Didn't you say you could carry me to win?
I'm about to lose my title
as the No. 1 Gongsun Li in Shapu!
If you have something to do, go ahead.
One minute you're in the bathroom,
the next you're on the phone.
Let's play another round.
I'm not playing with you anymore.
I dropped from Gold to Silver.
I've been reported so many times.
Let's rest.
We have serious business tomorrow.
Although I'm average at games,
I'll do a good job tomorrow.
Mr. Zhou.
Have you noticed anything different?
You?
Not me.
I mean the room. I redid the decor.
I've thought it through.
I'll pull myself together.
So I redecorated
the whole place.
Where?
Look at those posters.
This?
Those are not important.
Look.
Up here.
Global Elite—
Stephen Chow, "King of Comedy,"
the struggles of ordinary people
are the most moving.
I will use these posters
to motivate myself every day.
I'll start by becoming a village celebrity
and work my way up
to becoming
a Global Elite like Mr. Chow.
Please bless me.
Okay, you're well prepared.
Don't worry.
This time,
we will succeed.
Let's work hard together!
Don't wake them up.
It's okay.
Although Zhen seems careless,
she is actually the gentlest.
Is Ximei gonna mind?
It's fine.
She's a heavy sleeper.
She can sleep through anything.
Little crab.
Well,
I'm sorry about buying followers
last time.
Mr. Zhou,
actually,
I was too mean to you before.
It's okay.
I think
my emotions are not stable enough.
I bought a book.
Mr. Cat in the Western-Style House.
Who has the most stable emotions?
The cats.
I want to learn from them.
Okay, study hard.
Jiahao.
I have to thank you guys.
Actually, it feels quite different
coming back this time.
At first,
we just wanted to make some money.
But after spending all this time
with you and doing
all these things together,
it feels quite different.
From now on,
I will definitely treat
your business as my own—
You're really emotionally stable.
[Zhen, work hard.]
[Tomorrow's Performance: Thunderstorm]
Chief,
why are you here, too?
The reporter is here.
How could he not come?
Right?
Watch your mouth.
I was afraid you wouldn't understand
the situation in the village.
If I hadn't been here last time
the reporters came,
would it have gone so smoothly?
Right?
By the way, let me ask.
W-What are you guys planning to do next?
Well, we're
still working on it.
So...
y-you don't actually have a plan?
Well, what are we going to do then?
Wait, how can you not have a plan?
Village Chief.
We meet again.
Hello, Reporter Du.
Hello.
Let me do the introductions. This is Zhou.
Zhou... you know, Zhou.
Yes. Yes. Yes.
Hello.
Reporter Du.
I've seen your videos.
Nice to meet you.
Today, Reporter Du—
Hello, Reporter Du.
Hello.
Yes.
Hello, I'm Lin Ximei.
She hasn't met you yet.
I'm Mr. Zhou's agent.
Hello.
Well,
you are here specifically
to interview him today.
Yes.
Then I'll get back to work.
I wish you a successful interview.
Cooperate well.
Aren't you going
to chat with us for a while?
They are here to interview Zhou.
I'll leave you to it. Just play along,
alright? Do a good job.
He loves being interviewed the most.
Yeah.
He doesn't know our future plans,
so he can't rush to answer.
Right.
Then let's begin.
Okay.
Come on, let's get ready.
Liu, make sure you
get the focus right this time.
Half the footage was
out of focus last time.
Hello, everyone online.
I'm very happy
to have Mr. Zhou
and his team here with us today.
So
I'd like to ask Mr. Zhou a question.
What made you choose such a bold,
no-holds-barred approach
to promote our village
as the hometown of "King of Comedy"?
You could practically be called
the father of the hometown
of "King of Comedy."
No, I don't deserve that.
I really don't deserve that.
Mainly it's...
The mother of the hometown
of "King of Comedy".
No, no.
I'm the son of the former village chief
of the hometown of "King of Comedy."
I'm the cousin of that "father,"
so I guess that makes me the "Cousin."
Okay.
Then I'd like to ask a question here.
As far as I know...
Mr. Zhou is not from this village.
Yes.
Why did you work so hard
to promote this village?
Mainly,
we were moved by the villagers' passion...
and their sincerity.
Plus, as professionals,
we deliver exactly what we're paid for.
They were very "generous."
No, no, no.
It's about passion!
Enthusiasm.
It's everyone's love
for "King of Comedy."
It's
all about love!
Love.
Since,
well,
you've already
shot the short video.
You two,
have you ever thought about
taking it a step further?
This, this...
We're not in that kind of relationship.
We've only known each other
for a few days.
I don't mean your relationship.
I mean, since you've
already shot a short video,
why haven't you thought
about making a feature film?
Never thought about it.
That won't do.
You've gotta think about it.
Think about it.
Nowadays, many film and television works,
like "The Knockout,"
"To the Wonder,"
"City of Rock,"
have all used movies or TV shows
to put their villages on the map.
You could totally copy them.
Follow their lead.
But none of us here
have ever made a movie.
We don't know how.
We can't make one.
According to our investigation,
Mr. Zhou Ke
has directed a film before.
You've directed a movie?
Then let's make one.
Let's make a movie.
Y-You're mistaken.
I've been a tour guide,
not a director.
No way. I've got a screenshot right here.
Same name. Same name.
You've gained a lot of weight now.
Look, isn't this you?
Indeed.
He's directed before
and made some excellent films.
But now he wants to try something new.
Because as the saying goes,
"A good actor can become a director.
And a good director
can do just about anything," right?
We'll handle everything
from planning
and production
to executive producing.
You could say...
it's excellent!
In that case,
Director Zhou,
could you
tell us a little more about it?
How do you plan to shoot it?
Director Zhou,
Director Zhou, Director Zhou.
Come on.
I-I'll go to the restroom first.
You guys do the interview first.
Director Zhou.
Let me help you.
You just said," To the Rock,"
"The Wonder Band,"
and a "K" something?
You didn't remember a single one?
"The Kickout."
It's okay.
Ke.
Here,
let me give you a hug.
Mr. Zhou!
Sit, sit, sit.
Come.
Mr. Zhou.
Well.
Director Zhou.
Please, you don't need to call me that.
Don't call me that.
Just now,
I came up with
a brilliant
idea.
What idea?
That is...
making a movie!
Jiahao.
Isn't that what the reporter thought of?
I thought of it a long time ago.
He just said it
one second before me.
Director Zhou.
Hear me out.
We want to leverage our identity
as the hometown
of "King of Comedy"
to make a film of our own.
Let's call it
"King of Comedy"!
Well,
that film already exists.
Then let's call it
"The New King of Comedy"!
That also exists.
New, new, new...
It's not about what it's called.
Well...
"The Brand New King of Comedy"!
It's awful, very awful!
Why?
M-Making a movie is not that simple.
First of all,
you need actors to make a movie, right?
We don't have actors.
We have ready-made ones—
Yudan,
Shengzai.
Director Zhou personally selected them
-Yes.
-as actors.
Besides,
all the villagers can be used by you.
E-Even if we have actors,
we need equipment for shooting, right?
Where are we supposed
to get all those
big machines and cameras?
It has 50 million pixels
and is the pride of domestic phones.
Okay.
For this production,
we need
professionals.
And the most professional person
is sitting right here.
Director Zhou is
our most professional person.
Once it's done,
where are we
gonna show it?
We don't need to release it.
Then who will watch it?
Put it out.
Put it on the internet.
We don't need others to watch this movie.
We are using the movie
to make our village popular.
Then, then,
then,
here comes the most important question.
Making a movie requires money, right?
We can
get the whole village
to crowdfund it.
Don't even start with that crowdfunding
and fundraising nonsense.
You talk them
into coughing up the cash upfront,
saying it as a joint venture,
and when it flops,
you're left drowning in debt!
You think being in debt is easy?
All you can do is stare at the bills...
Ms. Lin, I don't like listening to you.
You're such a buzzkill.
I now announce
that we will have
Director Zhou give an opening speech.
W-We're starting to shoot?
I think
making a movie
is indeed a good idea.
See?
I-It can create hype.
But...
Maybe
I won't participate.
Maybe you should find someone else.
Or I can introduce someone to you.
Okay?
Y-You guys discuss it further.
She also knows a lot of people.
I'll just go out for a bit.
Mr. Zhou.
You guys discuss it first.
Ke.
Mr. Zhou.
Did you see that?
Ke.
The aura of a great director
is already showing.
I'll go talk to Director Zhou first.
Director Zhou.
Is something wrong with Mr. Zhou?
Ke
was hurt by movies.
Where was he hurt?
His heart.
It
all goes back to that one time...
[During a spring meant for rebirth...]
[Certificate of Honor: Excellent Graduate]
[I want to make a movie.]
[Global Blockbuster "Husky Man" Wraps]
[King of Bad Movies]
Can I watch
Mr. Zhou's movie?
J-Just don't watch it.
Oh no!
It's not even finished editing.
Oh no.
What's wrong?
Oh no, oh no.
Director Zhou ran too fast.
I couldn't catch him.
How did you find me?
I wasn't looking for you.
You don't need to persuade me.
I'm not persuading you.
Then why are you here?
This is my turf.
I'm the one
who brought you here in the first place.
Sorry then.
I won't take up your space, then.
I'm leaving now.
Bye-bye.
I'm leaving.
About this movie idea...
I think you should think twice.
I didn't actually finish
the story I told you last time.
My friend...
later...
Let me tell you a story.
It's very similar to yours.
There was a dog in our village.
♪ Lost in the crowds, we carry on ♪
It was small, black,
and adorable.
♪ Someone will stay
with you through day and night ♪
People around us
all called it Xiaoke.
♪ The art of loving and being loved ♪
One day, it went out
and walked and walked...
just like always.
♪ I'll give my all
to get it right for you ♪
Bam!
It got hit by a car.
♪ Who would risk it all for you? ♪
Since then,
it never dared to go out again.
♪ Locking all the sorrow deep inside ♪
After a while,
♪ Like a clown who can become ♪
the dog finally
pulled itself together,
summoned its courage,
and walked out that door.
♪ The superhero who makes you smile ♪
And then?
It died.
♪ Oh, time ♪
♪ People who live like clowns ♪
What a wonderful story.
♪ Have long forgotten the dust
on their sleeves ♪
What a roller coaster.
♪ With honest hearts,
we make this world more tender ♪
You really aren't here to persuade me.
Anyway,
when it comes to making a movie,
♪ Oh, time ♪
you guys...
I'll be the director.
♪ We who were once loved by clowns ♪
You? You're directing?
♪ Can become superheroes too ♪
Can you even direct?
No.
♪ Saving every inch of sorrow ♪
Then how are you gonna direct it?
Isn't that what you're here for?
♪ Then the world is whole again ♪
I am?
Haven't you always been here?